[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle：这会感觉很奇怪
&gt;&gt; Kyle: This is going to feel strange and
对于那些以前没有使用过发电机的人来说，这很奇怪。
bizarre to those of you that haven't worked with generators before.
所以，就像其他事情一样，我的建议并不是
So, just like everything else, what I'm suggesting to you is not
五分钟后你将成为这个模式的专家。
in five minutes you're going to be an expert on this pattern.
但我想告诉你，如果你真的相信我，
But I'm trying to suggest to you, if you trust me at all,
相信我，这是你应该花大量时间思考的地方，而且
trust me that this is where you should spend a whole bunch of time thinking, and
练习和阅读
practicing, and reading,
因为它将改变我们所做的一切，使用异步编程。
because it's going to change everything that we do, with asynchronous programming.
我100%相信这是我们语言最具革命性的变化之一。
I'm 100% convinced it's one of the most revolutionary changes to our language.
这就是我们花时间思考的原因。
That's why we spend time thinking about it.
好吧。
Okay.
因此，如果我们可以在生成器运行时暂停它，它也是消息传递。
So, if we can pause a generator while it's running, it's also message passing.
所以在这里，我不只是调用收益，而是用一个值来调用收益。
So here, I'm not just calling yield but I'm actually calling yield with a value.
在前面的例子中，当我在产量表达式中没有显示任何值时，
In the previous case, when I showed no value in the yield expression,
有人认为我的让步是不确定的。
it was assumed that I was yielding undefined.
但在这里我得到的是实际值，如1、2和3，以及
But here I'm yielding actual values like 1, 2, and 3, and
您注意到，当我调用product1时，我将控制权返回到第9行。
you notice that when I call yield 1, I return control back to line 9.
通过返回值的方式.Next作为对象返回。
By way of returning a value .next returns as an object.
上面有两个属性。
That has two properties on it.
它有一个Value属性和所产生的值(如果有的话)。
It has a value property with the value that was yielded, if any.
它有一个完成属性，告诉我们生成器是完成的是真还是假。
And it has a done property that tells us true or false is the generator complete.
所以这就是我们得到价值的地方：1，完成：假。
So that's where we get value: 1, done: false.
然后我们可以打电话，下一次马上或稍后再打。
And then we can call .next again right away or at some later time.
我们将得到价值：2，完成：瀑布，我们想再次调用它，得到3。
And we're gonna get value: 2, done: falls, and we want to call it again and yield 3.
在那一刻，它在视觉上看起来有点像生成器完成了，但是
At that moment, it kind of looks to you visually like the generator is done, but
还没有真正完成。
it's not really done.
这就是为什么我们仍然完成了：错误，
That's why we still get done: false,
因为从技术上讲，它暂停在最后一个表达式上。
because technically it's paused on that last expression.
即使在视觉上，我们可以看到发电机
Even though visually, we can look at the generator and
假设它不会做任何其他事情，从技术上讲，它仍然处于暂停状态。
say it's not going to do anything else, technically it's still paused.
从技术上讲，你仍然可以用它做一些事情。
Technically, you can still do something with it.
所以这就是为什么第四个。下一个13号线
So that's why the fourth .next down there on line thirteen
将恢复暂停行4的生成器。
would resume the generator of the pause line four.
马上，就没有别的事可做了。
Immediately, there is nothing else to do.
它会完成，它会完成。
It would finish, it would complete.
然后我们会得到一个对象，它没有给我们任何价值，但是
And then we would get an object back that there was no value given to us but
有一个完成：真的。
there was a done: true.
那么这个值呢：undefined。
Now what about that value: undefined.
你认为这是从哪里来的？
Where do you suppose that comes from?
它的来源是在JavaScript中，所有没有返回值的函数
Where it comes from is that in JavaScript, all functions that don't have a return
语句在末尾隐含未定义的返回。
statement imply a return undefined at the end.
因此，在第四行半中有一个未定义的隐含回报。
So, there's an implied return undefined on line four and a half.
如果我们选择不同的返回值，例如，
Had we chosen to do a different return value, like for example,
返回4，我们将获得完成的价值：是的。
return four, we would have gotten value for done: true.
在13号线。这有意义吗？
On line 13. Does that make sense?
因此，在任何时候，当您从生成器返回时，都会立即完成
So, at any point when you do a return from a generator, you immediately complete
生成器，并且您返回的任何内容都将作为值发送出去。
the generator, and whatever you've returned is sent out as the value.
但是，如果你做了一个收益，值被发送出去，你得到了一个完成：FALSE。
But if you do a yield, the value is sent out and you get a done: false.
是吗？
Yeah?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：您可以迭代它，将每个作为集合执行a，并获得值和
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Can you iterate it, do a for each as a collection and get the value and
东西一次移动一次下一个？
stuff moving one .next at a time?
&GT；&GT；Kyle：对不起，也许可以问这个问题-
&gt;&gt; Kyle: I'm sorry, maybe ask the question-
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：你正在做。接下来，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You're doing it.next,
你就得到了价值。
and you get the value.
然后你做一个迭代器，接下来，你得到下一个值？
Then you do an iterator .next, you get the next value?
凯尔：是的。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：相反，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Yeah. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Instead,
我们可以循环吗，像四个每个循环，就像一个集合？
can we loop through, like a four each loop, like a collection?
&gt；&gt；Kyle：你能自动运行整个迭代器吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Can you automatically run through a whole iterator?
当然，这实际上什么都没有，不是关于发电机的。
Absolutely, that's actually got nothing, not specifically about generators.
它可以是任何迭代器。
It's any iterator.
可以通过循环运行。
Can be run through a loop.
你可以像那样做你自己的四个眼圈。
You could do your own four eye loop like that.
你可能在寻找完成的：真实的事情，
You could be looking for the done: true thing,
就像查找done的while循环：true。
like a while loop looking for done: true.
但ES6中增加了一种新的循环样式，专门用于
But there was a new looping style added to ES6, specifically for
消耗迭代器，这是循环的四个。
consuming iterators, and it's the four of loop.
所以，不是四个或四个结束，我们现在有一个四个循环。
So, instead of four or four end, we now have a four of loop.
如果你给它一个迭代器，即使是来自生成器的迭代器，
And if you give it an iterator, even one from a generator,
如果给它一个迭代器，它将运行迭代器直到完成。
if you give it an iterator, it will run the iterator to completion.
并且它会自动查找Done：false以及所有这些内容。
And it automatically looks for the done: false and all that stuff.
因此，如果您想使用迭代器，有一个循环语法。
So, if you want to consume an iterator there is a looping syntax for it.
所以，这是一种非常同步的语法，它可以或者
So, that's a very synchronous syntax which may or
可能不是你想要的发电机。
may not be what you want with the generator.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：好的，那么
&gt;&gt; Kyle: All right, so
这清楚地说明了消息是可以传递的。
this is clearly illustrating that messages can be passed out.
但是，事实证明，这不仅是单向消息传递，而且实际上
But, it turns out that this is not only a one- way message passing, but actually
它们在下一对中一起产生，以创建双向消息传递系统。
they yield in the next pair together to create a two-way message passing system.
因此，我们不仅可以产生消息，而且当我们调用下一个方法时
So, not only can we yield messages out, but when we call the next method
我们可以传递一条消息，然后该消息进入生成器。
we can pass a message in, and that message goes into the generator.
我将为自己创建一个小帮手，以节省幻灯片上的空间。
I'm going to create a little helper for myself just to save space on the slides.
不要太沉迷于这是什么，但它是围绕着一个生成器。
Don't get too wrapped up in what this is, but it's wrapping around a generator.
您可以看到，在第2行，我正在执行生成器来生成迭代器。
You see on line 2, I'm executing my generator to produce an iterator.
然后我返回一个函数，每次调用该函数时，
And then I'm returning a function that every time that function gets called,
它将调用迭代器。下一步，传入任何参数并返回任何值OUT。
it's going to call the iterators.next pass in any arguments and return any value out.
所以，我只是在结束内幕。接下来，一些有点
So, I'm just wrapping up the interator.next ,something that's a little
更干净，更容易说明。
cleaner and easier to illustrate with.
但是任何时候你看到这个的用法，
But any time you see the usage of this,
你可以认为它只是在召唤。下一个在被子里，好吗？
you can just think it's just calling.next under the covers, okay?
&gt；&gt；Kyle：所以这个小帮手。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So this little helper.
我要把我的发电机传给它
I'm gonna pass my generator to it,
我所得到的将会是一个我称之为奔跑的东西。
and what I get back is going to be a thing I call run.
因此，run是一个函数。
So, run is a function.
每次我调用run，它就会调用下一个迭代器。
Every time I call run, it's calling the iterators next.
所以每当你看到跑，这东西它下一个点。
So whenever you see run, this thing IT dot next.
好的，所以我还没有在第1行的生成器中运行任何东西，但是
All right, so I haven't run anything in my generator on line 1, but
我只是简单地设置了这个要执行的生成器。
I've simply set up this generator to be executed.
在7号线上，我将呼叫第一轮。
And on line 7, I'm going to call the first run.
这是我第一次打下一个电话，而且
That's the first I teed up next call, and
它将把控制权转移到2号线。
it's going to transfer control up to line 2.
现在第二行，它将开始执行var X=1+和
Now on line two, it's going to start to execute as a var X equals one plus and
我看到了屈服的表情。
I see a yield expression.
此时此刻，我无法完成这份声明。
I cannot complete this statement at this moment.
所以，我真的要在中间暂停发电机
So, I'm literally going to pause the generator right in the middle of this
声明，然后等别人恢复我的简历，好的。
statement, and wait for somebody to resume me, okay.
因此，YERVER关键字将把控制权返回到第七行。
So, that yield keyword is going to return control to line seven.
现在，返回的值是IT点下一个返回值，我们将在这里看到
Now, that value that came back the IT dot next return value that we would see here
将是一个表示，
would be an object that says,
值未定义，因为我们没有产生任何东西，Done：false。
value undefined because we didn't yield anything, done: false.
大家都跟我一起吗？
Is everybody with me?
值未定义，完成：FALSE。
Value undefined, done: false.
如果我们做出了一些有价值的东西，无论我们的产出是什么
Had we yielded something that would have been value whatever we yielded and
仍然完成：错误。
still done: false.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：但我想在这里稍微调整一下你的大脑，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: But here's where I want to tweak your brain a little bit,
因为这都是帮助你理解的视角，
because this is all about perspective that helps you understand,
为您提供了一条理解这一点的途径。
gives you a path for understanding this.
我要你做的是
What I want you to do is,
我想让你思考的角度，而不是来自外部世界。
I want you to think about the perspective not from the outside world.
因为外面的世界是我们通常会怎么想的。
Because the outside world is how we typically would think about it.
我们考虑通过我们的运行调用来驱动这个发电机。
We think about driving this generator by our run calls.
想让你从内部的角度来思考。
Want you to think about it from the inside perspective.
从发电机里发生的事情来看，我也在线了，而且
From what's happening in the generator at the moment that I am online too ,and
我遇到了一个关键的产量关键字在这个产量关键字是问一个问题。
I encounter a yield keyword essential in this yield keyword is asking a question.
它是说，我需要一些价值在这里。
It is saying, I need some value here.
这就像占位符说，我需要一些价值，但我还没有。
It's like a placeholder that says, I need some value and I don't have it yet.
我要一直等到有人给我一个值。
I'm going to wait around until somebody gives me a value.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：因为我显然需要一个值来结束语句。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Because I obviously need a value to finish the statement.
大家都同意吗？
Does everybody agree with that?
好吧。所以，我只是暂停等待
Okay. So, I'm simply going to pause waiting for
一个值，我会告诉你外面的世界，我问了一个问题。
a value, and I will tell you outside world that I've asked a question.
我要求你给我一个价值。
I am asking for you to give me a value.
在稍后的某个点，如第8行，
At some later point like line 8,
我们将通过发回一个值来回答这个问题。
we're going to answer that question by sending a value back in.
值为10的值将会进来，并将替换或
And that value 10, will come in and will replace or
用该值完成生成表达式。
complete that yield expression with that value.
所以，现在生成器可以继续并且
So, now the generator can resume and
它可以完成它的工作，因为它说，谢谢你回答我的问题。
it can finish its work cuz it says, thank you for answering my question.
我问题的答案是价值十。
The answer to my question was value ten.
所以，现在我可以把十加一在一起，x是11。
So, now I can add ten and one together and x is 11.
从内部的角度来看，这是你想要的关键视角。
From the inside perspective, that's the key perspective you wanna have.
不要想太多外面发生的事情，因为外面的东西
Don't think so much about what's happening on the outside because the outside stuff
最终会被埋葬在某个图书馆里。
is actually going to end up being buried away in some library.
重要的是里面的东西。
It's the inside stuff that matters.
这是发生在发电机内部的事情。
It's what's happening on the inside of the generator.
我在问题。
I'm asking a question.
现在，我在这里问了一个非常简单的问题。
Now, here I asked a very simple question.
我刚说了让步。
I just said yield.
我说给我一些价值。
I said give me some value.
但是，如果我的问题就像是进行Ajax调用，又会怎样呢？
But what if my question was like making an AJAX call.
我说我需要一个Ajax调用的响应。
And I said I need a response from an AJAX call.
我不知道要花多长时间，
And I don't know how long it's going to take,
但我会一直等着直到你给我回复。
but I'll just wait around until you give me a response.
因此，我们可以生成一个Ajax调用。
So, we could have yielded an AJAX call.
好吧。
Okay.
因此，我们以值10的方式发回了一个答案。
So, we've sent an answer back in by way of value ten.
X现在是11，我们去第三行。
X is now 11, we go to line three.
我们开始执行一个加号，然后再加上另一个关键字。
We start executing like one plus and then another yield keyword.
所以，我们在问另一个问题，这意味着我们要停下来
So, we're asking another question, which means we're gonna pause and
等待答案，我们将把控制权返回到8号线。
wait for that answer, and we're gonna return control back to line eight.
第八行将说，将有一个对象值，未定义完成：false。
Line eight is gonna say, is gonna have an object value, undefined done: false.
就像七号线一样。
Just like line seven.
稍后，我们将回答这个悬而未决的问题
At some later point, we're gonna answer that pending question
通过传入值30，就像我们在第10行所做的那样。
by passing in the value 30 as we're doing on line ten.
所以值30会回来
So that value 30 is going to come back and
完成第三行等待的产出率表达式。
complete the yield expression that was waiting on line three.
现在，30可以加到1上，现在y是31。
Now, 30 can be added to one, and now y is 31.
X以前设置为11。
X was previously set to 11.
而现在，即使它与所有这些箭头混淆，
And now, even though it's confusing with all these arrows,
第四行将输出一个值。
line four is going to yield out a value.
你看，有一个值，我计算x加y。
You see, there is a value that I compute x plus y.
它立即被计算出来，也就是值42。
It gets computed right away which is the value 42.
所以，这就是我提出的值为42的问题。
So, that's me asking the question with the value 42.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：所以，我想发出值42，这就是为什么我可以说点值，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So, I want to send out the value 42, and that's why I can say dot value,
因为我得到了一个对象，表示值42完成：false。
cuz I got an object that said value 42 done: false.